<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TruthGame</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="add_player_text">Add player</string>
    <string name="player_card">Player card</string>
    <string name="no_players_registered">No players registered!</string>
    <string name="clear_lobby">Clear lobby</string>
    <string name="start_game">Start game</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="user_picture">User picture</string>
    <string name="yellow_crayola">Yellow crayola</string>
    <string name="sandy_brown">Sandy brown</string>
    <string name="buff">Buff</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="choose_color">Choose color:</string>
    <string name="update_player_text">Update player</string>
    <string name="score">Score: %1$s</string>
    <string name="add_question">Add question</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "What's the point of TruthGame? Well, a question you've registered is going to be asked to one of the players. The player then has"
        "to answer this question in a way that the other player's find truthful and/or introspective. If they do, they'll give the answer a thumbs up."
        "The player then gets one score point, and the game continues in the same way."
        "Since this game is about telling the truth, it's important that that everyone who is playing is comfortable with the questions given to them and don't feel pressured into answering"
        "anything they don't want to. Remember that a question can always be skipped by shaking the phone. Also,"
        "it is not recommended to play this game in combination with alcohol. TruthGame is supposed to be"
        "a way for you and your friends to get to know each other more, and is meant for calm and safe social environments. \n\n"

        "So how do you start playing? First things first, you need to add some questions that you want to ask your friends."
        "This is done by navigating to "My questions" in the top right corner of your screen. It's a good idea to add a few questions"
        "beforehand to playing the game with your friends, as then you'll have time to come up with some really good ones."
        "These questions are saved between games so if you're having a dull moment on your commute, you could always try"
        "coming up with some more. \n\n"

        "When you've got some questions you need to register players. This is done by pressing the plus icon from the main screen."
        "You need to be at least two people in order to play TruthGame, as playing it by yourself probably wouldn't be fun at all."
        "When this is done, you can get to playing by starting the game from the main screen. \n\n"

        "And remember, even though this game keeps track of your score the goal is never to win. Listen to your friends answers,"
        "discuss and hopefully at some point put down the phone and stop playing. Good luck!"

    </string>
    <string name="show_rules">Show rules</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="my_questions">My questions</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="play_game">Play game</string>
    <string name="player_name">Player name</string>
    <string name="thumbs_up">Thumbs up</string>
    <string name="thumbs_down">Thumbs down</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="you_need_to_add_questions">You need to add questions!</string>
    <string name="no_questions_added_yet">No questions added yet!</string>
</resources>